
ff: parsing domain file
domain 'AGENCIA_VIAJES' defined
 ... done.
ff: parsing problem file
problem 'ITINERARIO_BASICO_LARGO' defined
 ... done.


translating negated cond for predicate VISITADA
translating negated cond for predicate VIAJE-EMPEZADO
warning: numeric goal. turning cost-minimizing relaxed plans OFF.

ff: search configuration is weighted A* with weight 1.
Metric is ((1.00*[RF0](CIUDADES-VISITADAS)) - () + 0.00)
COST MINIMIZATION DONE (WITHOUT cost-minimizing relaxed plans).

advancing to goal distance:    4
                               3
                               2
                               1
                               0

ff: found legal plan as follows
step    0: EMPEZAR-VIAJE LONDRES H_LON
        1: VOLAR-Y-ALOJAR LONDRES ROMA H_ROM
        2: VOLAR-Y-ALOJAR ROMA PARIS H_PAR
        3: VOLAR-Y-ALOJAR PARIS MADRID H_MAD
plan cost: 4.000000

time spent:    0.01 seconds instantiating 15 easy, 0 hard action templates
               0.00 seconds reachability analysis, yielding 22 facts and 15 actions
               0.00 seconds creating final representation with 22 relevant facts, 1 relevant fluents
               0.00 seconds computing LNF
               0.00 seconds building connectivity graph
               0.00 seconds searching, evaluating 10 states, to a max depth of 0
               0.01 seconds total time

